lover.ly 2019-01-18

# About Loverly Partnerships

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy, and the privacy of all registered users of Lover.ly ("Lover.ly" or the "Site"), is important to us. Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy. Our policy is based on the principles of notice and choice in the collection and use of information regarding our users and their activities on the Site. This privacy policy tells you what information we gather from you, how we may use or disclose that information and our efforts to protect it. Please read this policy carefully, and feel free to contact us at privacy@Lover.ly or at the mailing address set forth below if you have any questions regarding its content.

In connection with use of the Site and the services provided in connection with the Site (such services and Site, collectively, the "Service"), we ask for and may collect a variety of information in the following ways. 

 **Log Data**

Our servers may automatically record non-personally identifiable information ("Log Data") from anyone who uses the Service or visits the Site. This Log Data may include the visitor's IP address, browser type, operating system and language settings, referring domain, pages visited, visit duration and submitted search terms. This data is used to monitor Site usage, conduct Site administration and troubleshooting, and assist in improvements to the Service. We may vary and tailor the content the visitor receives in future visits to the Site based on such visitor's preferences and activities as determined based upon such Log Data.

 **Registration and Account Data**

If you register to use the Site, we ask for and store information you provide such as your email, first name, last name, username, mailing address, billing address, role in the wedding, gender, city, country, wedding date, mobile phone, type of wedding, wedding guest count, wedding budget, your Facebook handle, your Twitter handle, and a profile photo of yourself (collectively, Registration Data). You may also be presented with the option to register to use the Site using Facebook Connect, and if you choose to do so, your Facebook profile information will be imported to, and become a part of, your Registration Data. Only email, first name, last name, username, role in the wedding, city and country are required entries. Your profile photo, mobile phone number, type of wedding, guest count, wedding budget, Facebook handle and Twitter handle will only be displayed if you elect to do so through your Account Settings page. After you register to use the Site, you may set up your personal profile, interact with other users of the Site, and transmit information through various channels ("Account Data"). We collect and retain this information so that we can provide you the Service and offer personalized features, including varying the content you receive in future visits to the Site based on your preferences and activities and viewing interaction history. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time.

Although the Service may permit you to make purchases from third-party providers, such transactions are with those third-party providers directly. We may share certain of your information with such providers in order for you to engage with them and complete transactions. Although the Service may appear to collect payment card information in connection with transactions, Lover.ly does not possess or store such information, with such information instead being sent directly to the vendor at issue and/or the vendor’s payment processor.

 **Combination of Log Data and Registration Data**

Log Data may be combined with a user's username, Registration Data and Account Data once a user has registered or subsequently logged into the Site. The combined data is used to provide, monitor and assist in improvements to the Service, and customize content and advertising displayed to the user on the Site and on other sites that participate in Lover.ly's advertising network. The Account Data, Registration Data, and combined data will not be shared with third parties except in the case of third party service providers and legal processes, as noted below.

 **Cookies**

Use of certain features on Lover.ly requires that Site users accept the use of cookies, which are small data files that the Site sends to the visitor's browser for storage on such visitor's computer's hard drive. We use cookies to protect confidential data, track activity at the Site and better serve Visitors' needs, preferences and interests as noted above. Third party ads displayed on Lover.ly and on other sites that participate in the Lover.ly advertising network may also contain cookies set by the advertiser, ad network or their agent. Lover.ly does not control these cookies. Users of Lover.ly should consult the privacy policies of the advertiser, ad network or their agent to learn how they use cookies.

Information Collected on Behalf of Advertisers and Publishers

Non-personally identifiable information that we collect may be used to provide reports to advertisers and publishers who participate in Lover.ly's advertising network, to schedule, deliver and optimize advertisements, and to help Lover.ly display and customize advertisements to the interests or preferences of Site visitors and to visitors of the publisher sites who participate in Lover.ly's advertising network.

Information Collected From Advertisers and Publishers

We may collect non-personally identifiable and personally identifiable information from advertisers and publishers who participate in Lover.ly's advertising network. Such information may be used for internal analysis in order to perform and improve the Service and associated technologies, and to operate and improve the Site. Publisher and advertiser registration information may be used by Lover.ly to provide customer support to the applicable advertiser or publisher, and to send to such party account-related information, including invoices, payments, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support, administrative and promotional messages.

 **Aggregate Information**

We may share aggregate information with advertisers, publishers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties in a manner that does not identify any particular advertiser, publisher or end user.

 **Submitted Content**

You post content on the Site at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your Registration Data and Site activities, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Site users with whom you may choose to share your information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of content you post may remain viewable in cached and archived pages on the Internet or if other Site users have copied or stored content you post. Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Lover.ly is a violation of the Lover.ly Terms of Service and should be reported via privacy@Lover.ly.

 **Legal Compliance**

We may disclose information to fulfill legal or regulatory requirements or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others' rights or to prevent harm.

 **Third Party Service Providers**

We retain certain third party service providers to perform functions and services to us. We may share your personal information with these third party service providers, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and services, and only pursuant to obligations that are no less restrictive than those contained in this privacy policy.

Security

Lover.ly uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard personally identifying information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk.

Minimum Age

Users of the Site must be at least 13 years of age. We do not knowingly accept registrations from users that are under 13. We will delete accounts of any users that we find to be under-age. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information or is using the Service without your consent, please contact us at privacy@Lover.ly. If you are aware that any child under the age of 13 has become a registered user, please inform us at privacy@Lover.ly, so that we can confirm and take the appropriate steps to remove the account and any related information.

 **Communication**

Lover.ly may send to registered users, advertisers and publishers Service and/or account activity-related announcements from time to time.

Changing Your Registration Information and/or Newsletter Subscription

You can access or update your personal information, including subscriptions to our email newsletters, at any time. To unsubscribe, you can follow the instructions on the bottom of each newsletter. You can also edit your privacy preferences in your member profile. If you would like to cancel your account with Lover.ly, please contact Member Services by emailing hello@lover.ly and writing "Cancel Account" in the subject line. You may also write to Lover.ly Member Services at:

Dubblee Media Inc

New York, NY 10010   

USA 

 **Changes to Privacy Policy**

It may be necessary from time to time for us to modify this policy to reflect changes in the way we collect and use information or changes in privacy-related laws, regulations, and industry standards. Accordingly, we reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting the revised policy on this Site. Data will be handled in accordance with the policy in effect at the time the data is used.

 **Our mailing address is:**

 **Dubblee Media Inc**

New York, NY 10010   

USA
